code completion is a simple feature in
代码完成是的一个简单功能
many ideas that developers may take for
开发人员可能会采纳的许多想法
granted but really has a lot of powerful
理所当然但确实有很多强大的功能
functionality built into it let's take a
内置的功能让我们来
look at how basic code completion works
看一下基本代码完成的工作原理
in IntelliJ IDEA so intelligent idea
在IntelliJ IDEA中这么聪明的想法
index is your entire project and when
索引是您的整个项目以及何时
you write code it updates the completion
你写代码，它更新完成
list and gives you a visual reference so
列出并给您直观的参考
that as you're typing you're getting
当您输入内容时，
constant feedback from the IDE you're
来自您的IDE的持续反馈
directly interacting with the syntax
直接与语法进行交互
tree and can focus on the larger picture
树，可以专注于大图
of composing ideas rather than
构想而不是
keystrokes
击键
this works for statically as well as
这既适用于静态
dynamically typed languages so that as
动态键入的语言，以便
soon as you add a symbol you can
添加符号后，您就可以
immediately reference that later on
稍后再参考
although instant completion is available
尽管可以立即完成
whenever you use the dot operator you
每当您使用点运算符时，
can bring it up manually by pressing
可以通过按手动将其调出
control space to expand the basic
控制空间扩大基本
completion view which will show you all
完成视图将向您显示全部
of the index symbols language keywords
索引符号语言关键字的数量
and live templates as you can use in
和可以使用的实时模板
this scope inside this view there are a
此视图内的范围有一个
few things that you can do in order to
您可以做的几件事
select an entry you can simply press
选择一个条目，您只需按一下
ENTER and we'll complete that entry by
ENTER，我们将通过以下方式完成该输入
your cursor you can also exclude
您的光标也可以排除
individual entries from completion by
单个条目从完成起
selecting the entry and pressing alt
选择条目并按alt
enter to toggle the intention from here
输入以从此处切换意图
you can tell intelligent idea to exclude
你可以告诉聪明的主意排除
this entry and that preference will be
该条目和该首选项将是
added to your projects configuration so
已添加到您的项目配置中，因此
that it doesn't display it in the future
它不会在将来显示
you can also view quick documentation
您还可以查看快速文档
for any entry by pressing ctrl Q which
对于任何输入，请按ctrl Q，
will fetch the documentation for that
将为此获取文档
entry and display in a separate view
输入并在单独的视图中显示
which you can use for reference now by
您现在可以将其用作参考
default when you invoke basic completion
调用基本完成时的默认值
it will only show those entries that are
它只会显示那些
applicable in the local scope however if
适用于当地范围，但是如果
you'd like to expand that you can press
您想要扩展，可以按
it again and it will expand the list to
再次将其扩展到
include all of the classes available
包括所有可用的课程
through module dependencies inside your
通过您内部的模块依赖关系
project when you invoke basic completion
调用基本完成时的项目
a third time
第三次
it will expand the suggestion list to
它将建议列表扩展到
include all of the symbols in the
将所有符号包括在
language library and your entire project
语言库和您的整个项目
next we'll talk about smart completion
接下来我们将讨论智能完成
which will allow you to apply
这将使您可以申请
context-sensitive completion with full
上下文相关的完整完成
type inference
类型推断